Greece
Marist College
Greece
1789 1984
Marist Archives and Special Collections 3399 North Road, Poughkeepsie, New York 12601
Lowell Thomas
2.1.1.2.5
1203 Linear feet
Items in this collection do not circulate and may be used in-house only.
Glass plate negatives; Greece
- Lowell Thomas Papers
  - Graphic Materials, 2
    - Photographs, 2.1
      - Glass plate negatives, 2.1.1
        - Lowell Thomas, 2.1.1.2
          - Greece, 2.1.1.2.5
              - Old Greek pointing down to Athens, circa 1918; 20 (Box 1323)
                5x7
              - Old Greek talking to son at Acropolis, Athens, circa 1918; 21
              - Ruins at Athens, circa 1918; 22
              - Lowell Thomas and Harry Chase in front of the Parthenon, Athens, circa 1918; 23
              - Temple of Thesus, Athens, circa 1918; 24
              - Soldiers and tents in front of the Temple of Thesus, Athens, circa 1918; 25
              - Looking down on olive orchard, circa 1918; 26
              - Big tree on road through Greece, circa 1918; 27
              - Four Greek mountaineers, circa 1918; 28
                film
              - Diogenes on donkey, circa 1918; 29
              - Demosthenes man, circa 1918; 30
              - Old Greek man and daughter, circa 1918; 31
              - Two boys in traditional Greek clothes, dancing for crowd, circa 1918; 32
              - Serbian boy, circa 1918; 33
              - Man, in traditional costume, with woman and child, circa 1918; 34
              - Group of Greeks at fair, circa 1918; 35
              - Greek fair, circa 1918; 36
              - Man in traditional Greek costume sharing water with old man in shorts, circa 1918; 37
              - Man in traditional Greek costume talking to three soldiers, others nearby them, circa 1918; 38
              - Essed Pasha, with dog, circa 1918; 39
              - Russian diplomat in Serbian army at Salonica, circa 1918; 40
              - Panorama of Salonica, circa 1918; 41
              - View of Salonica from top of hill, boy and Lowell Thomas [?] in foreground, circa 1918; 42
              - Mound at Salonica, circa 1918; 43
              - Salonica street scene, circa 1918; 44
              - Bralos, tents and soldiers in foreground, circa 1918; 45
              - Tents on hillside, soldier in foreground, circa 1918; 46
              - Winding military road through mountains, soldier sitting on rock at right, circa 1918; 47
              - Janes Club, soldier by building, automobile at left, Macedonia, circa 1918; 48